RG 033, Works Progress Administration for Connecticut
Connecticut State Library
- Series 36. Publications
  - 106. File copies of W.P.A. publications, 1936-1942
    - Traffic safety and control (Box 330-331)
    - New Haven Community Chest and Council of Social agencies (Box 332)
    - Society for Research in Child Development (Box 332)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 333)